Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Legal Cases: Bailey, Dorothy C.: (1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 34)
  - Legal Cases: Bailey, Dorothy C.: (2 of 2):, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 35)
  - Legal Cases: Bauser, Clarence J. vs. OSU Hospitals, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 36)
  - Legal Cases: Blakely, Odessa, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 37)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Canteen Corporation, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 38)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Dana G. Rinehart, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 39)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Dept. of Administrative Services, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 40)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. James D Beaber, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 41)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. John Roberts, Inc., 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 42)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Lancaster Colony, Indiana Glass, and Friendly Ice Cream, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 43)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Sanford M Weinberg, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 44)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. Ward Warren Manuscripts, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 45)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Trustees vs. The Way International, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 46)
  - Legal Cases: Brown, Annie Mae, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 47)
  - Legal Cases: Campbell, Edward H. vs. Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 48)
  - Legal Cases: Cato, Charles P. vs. OSU, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 49)
  - Legal Cases: Coons, Glen D. vs. OSU, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 50)
  - Legal Cases: Cowan, Samuel, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0023, Folder 51)
  - Legal Cases: Covey, Ralph C., 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 1)
  - Legal Cases: Davis, Joseph E. vs. OSU Hospital, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 2)
  - Legal Cases: Diday, Mabel vs. OSU Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 3)
  - Legal Cases: Gaye, Martin: Breach of Contract, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 4)
  - Legal Cases: Gilmore, Vernon Scott vs. Droste, Paul E., 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 5)
  - Legal Cases: Glatt Johnena vs. OSU, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 6)
  - Legal Cases: Gouge, Ruth Marie vs. OSU Hospital, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 7)
  - Legal Cases: Greitzer, Nancy, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 8)
  - Legal Cases: Grimes, Deborah, and Callahan, Sandra, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 9)
  - Legal Cases: Groves, Jack vs. OSU College of Veterinary Medicine, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 10)
  - Legal Cases: Hayes, David T. vs. Board of Trustees, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 11)
  - Legal Cases: Hirsch, Gustav, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 12)
  - Legal Cases: Hughes, Charles L. vs. OSU, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 13)
  - Legal Cases: Johnson, Roger Eugene vs. OSU, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 14)
  - Legal Cases: Kessler, Francis, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 15)
  - Legal Cases: Kilgour, Marta vs. OSU Hospitals, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 16)
  - Legal Cases: Kottman, Roy: Retirement (OSU M-111), 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 17)
  - Legal Cases: Laver, James B. vs. OSU, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 18)
  - Metcald, Bruce L. vs. OSU Hospitals, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 19)
  - Legal Cases: Moots, Pamela S., 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 20)
  - Legal Cases: O'Brien, Charles William vs. OSU Lantern, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 21)
  - Legal Cases: Ohio Self-Employed Study Group vs. OSU Hospitals, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 22)
  - Legal Cases: OSU vs. Franklin County Auditor, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 23)
  - Legal Cases: OSU vs. Martin Painting, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 24)
  - Legal Cases: Ojalov, Anita vs. OSU, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 25)
  - Legal Cases: Ottinger vs. Riggs vs. Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 26)
  - Legal Cases: The Outlet Co. vs. Board of Trustees, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 27)
  - Legal Cases: Pace, William vs. Stiffy, et. al., 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 28)
  - Legal Cases: Robinson, Lizzie Mae, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 29)
  - Legal Cases: Robinson, Mary Ann vs. OSU, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 30)
  - Legal Cases: Shellow, Willie vs. OSU Hospitals, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 31)
  - Legal Cases: Sims, Vincent, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 32)
  - Legal Cases: Slappy, Carl vs. OSU, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 33)
  - Legal Cases: Smith, Agnes M., 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 34)
  - Legal Cases: Solid Rock Foundation vs. OSU, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 35)
  - Legal Cases: Spaulding, James D. vs. Harold Enarson and Madison Scott, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 36)
  - Legal Cases: States Electric Co. vs. OSU, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 37)
  - Legal Cases: Summary, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 38)
  - Legal Cases: Summary, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 39)
  - Legal Cases: Summary, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 40)
  - Legal Cases: Sunshine Law, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 41)
  - Legal Cases: Tague, Madeline Wilson vs. Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 42)
  - Legal Cases: Thiry, Alexander vs. Board of Trustees, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 43)
  - Walls, Robert L. vs. Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 44)
  - Legal Cases: Walters, Howard vs. OSU, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 45)
  - Legal Cases: Ware, Priscilla: Scott Hall Explosion, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 46)
  - Legal Cases: Weinberg, Sanford M., 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 47)
  - Legal Cases: Willey, Gerald A. vs. OSU Research Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 48)
  - Legal Cases: Williams, Harold, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 49)
  - Legal Cases: Williams, Lucille vs. University Cooperative Extension, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 50)
  - Legal Cases: Yashon, David vs. Hunt, William E., 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 51)
  - Legal Cases: York, Thomas, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 52)
  - Legal Cases: Zenker, William vs. Board of Trustees, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 53)
  - Legal Matters: Attorney General: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 54)
  - Legal Matters: Bailey Estate, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 55)
  - Legal Matters: Carley Cramer Estate, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 56)
  - Legal Matters: Carson, William N. Estate, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 57)
  - Legal Matters: Columbia Gas Allocation Problems, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 58)
  - Legal Matters: Costello Estate, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 59)
  - Legal Matters: Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 60)
  - Legal Matters: Fergus Will Contest, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 61)
  - Legal Matters: Fostoria Concrete Products, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 62)
  - Legal Matters: Grosser Estate, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 63)
  - Legal Matters: Hathaway Estate, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 64)
  - Legal Matters: Hirsch, Irene Estate, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 65)
  - Legal Matters: Holiday Inn Use of of OSU Initials in Advertising, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 66)
  - Legal Matters: Human Subjects in Research, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 67)
  - Legal Matters: Joyce, Glenna Estate, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 68)
  - Legal Matters: Kennedy Trust, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 69)
  - Legal Matters: Kincaid Estate, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 70)
  - Legal Matters: Liability Arising from Assault and Battery, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 71)
  - Legal Matters: Litigation Claims; Settlement, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 72)
  - Legal Matters: Mershon Will, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 73)
  - Legal Matters: Ohio Agricultural Research and Development Center Purchase of Jackson County Neville Farm, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 74)
  - Legal Matters: Personal Matters by the Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 75)
  - Legal Matters: Police Jurisdiction, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 76)
  - Legal Matters: Pomerene Hall Liquor Permit, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 77)
  - Legal Matters: Pooled Income Fund, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 78)
  - Legal Matters: Postal Service Litigation, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 79)
  - Legal Matters: Puchala, Alfred John, Sir, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 80)
  - Legal Matters: Purchell Estate, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 81)
  - Legal Matters: Saunders, Melville Estate, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 82)
  - Legal Matters: Starlin Trust, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 83)
  - Legal Matters: University Bookstores, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 84)
  - Legal Matters: Virgin Islands Property, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 85)
  - Legal Matters: Wayne County Equine Facility Lease, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0024, Folder 86)
  - Legislative Activities: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 1)
  - Libraries: Comparative Library Expenditures, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 2)
  - Libraries: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 3)
  - Libraries: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 4)
  - Libraries: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 5)
  - Libraries: Report: Retrospective Conversion of Bibliographic Records, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 6)
  - Libraries: Report: University Libraries for year 1971-1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 7)
  - Libraries: Search Committee for Director of Libraries, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 8)
  - Libraries: Voter Registration, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 9)
  - Library Council: Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln Tower, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Tower: Correspondence, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln Tower: Program of Requirements: Manpower Study: See Agriculture and Home Economics: College of, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 13)
  - Mathematics and Physical Science: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 14)
  - Medical Affairs: Monthly Reports: Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 15)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Association for Academic Health Centers, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 16)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Cancer Research Center, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 17)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 18)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 19)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Expansion of Facilities, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 20)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Grants, 1975-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 21)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Health Sciences Library, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 22)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Medical Student Transfers, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 23)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Practice Plan Committee, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 24)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Procedure for Corrective Action, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 25)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Proposed Cancer Center, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 26)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Proposed Procedure for Corrective Actions and Appellate: Review, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 27)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: University Hospitals, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 28)
  - Medical Affairs: Vice-President for: Veterans Administration Clinic, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 29)
  - Medical Practice Plan: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 30)
  - Medical Correspondence Plan: Court Documents, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 31)
  - Medical Practice Plan: Medicine: College of, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0025, Folder 32)
  - Medicine: College of: Clinical Medical Sciences Education Facility: Application of Federal Grant Assistance, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 1)
  - Medicine: College of: Comprehensive Cancer Program: Study, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 2)
  - Medicine: College of: Comprehensive Cancer Research Center: Correspondence Reports, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 3)
  - Medicine: College of: Clinical Medical Sciences Facility: Site Visit, 1975 September 7 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 4)
  - Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 5)
  - Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 6)
  - Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 7)
  - Medicine: College of: Hospital Expansion Matter, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 8)
  - Medicine: College of: Hogness, John: Visit, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 9)
  - Medicine: College of: Medical Practice Program Records at Archives, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 10)
  - Medicine: College of: Revenue Sources, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 11)
  - Medicine: College of: Search Committee: Dean of the College of Medicine, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 12)
  - Medicine: College of: Statistics, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 13)
  - Mershon Committee of Education in National Security, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 14)
  - Midwestern Universities Consortium for International Activities: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 15)
  - Midwestern Universities Consortium for International Activities: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 16)
  - Midwestern Universities Consortium for International Activities: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 17)
  - Minorities and Women on Campus: A Progress Report, 1974 December 9 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 18)
  - Minority Affairs: Office of: Correspondence and Reports, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 19)
  - Minority Affairs: Office of: Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 20)
  - Minority Affairs: Office of: Correspondence and Reports, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 21)
  - Music: School of: Faculty, Curriculum, and Facilities, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 22)
  - Music: School of: Glee Club, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 23)
  - Music: School of: Marching Band, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 24)
  - Music: School of: Scarlet and Gray Connection, 1975 June-July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 25)
  - Music: School of: Scholarships, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0026, Folder 26)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges: Conference on Science and Technology: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 1)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 2)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges: Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 3)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges: Financing of Postsecondary Education, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 4)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges: International Affairs Committee, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 5)
  - National Center for the Handicapped, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 6)
  - National Center for Research in Vocational Education, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 8)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): Minutes and Reports, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 9)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): Minutes and Reports, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 10)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): Official Inquiry: Allegations and Responses, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 11)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): Recruitment Allegations: Correspondence and Interviews, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA): NCAA Recruitment Allegations: See George E. Hill, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 13)
  - National Commission on Accrediting: Annual Meeting of Board of Commissioners, 1973 April 5-6 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 14)
  - National Commission on Accrediting: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 15)
  - National Merit: National Achievement Scholarship Program: Description and Proposals, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 16)
  - National Regulatory Research Institute, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 18)
  - National University Extension Association, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 19)
  - Natural Resources: School of: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 20)
  - Natural Resources: School of: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 21)
  - Nisonger Center (McCampbell Hall): Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 22)
  - North Central Association: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 23)
  - North Central Association: Institutional Annual Report, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 24)
  - North Central Association: Report: Coordination and Management of the Health Sciences, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 25)
  - North Central Association: Report: Of a Visit to OSU, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 26)
  - Northwood Community Center Cooperation, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 27)
  - Nursing: School of: Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0027, Folder 28)
  - Nursing: School of: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 1)
  - Nursing: School of: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 2)
  - Nursing: School of: Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 3)
  - Nursing: School of: Candidate for Director School of Nursing, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 4)
  - Nursing: School of: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 5)
  - Nursing: School of: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 6)
  - Nursing: School of: Curriculum Evaluations, 1976 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 7)
  - Nursing: School of: New Nursing Curriculum: Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 8)
  - Nursing: School of: Report: Implications of Converting the Nursing Faculty from 12-month to 9-month Contracts, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 9)
  - O'Hara, James G.: Congressman: Commencement Speeches, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 10)
  - Ohio: State of: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 11)
  - Ohio: State of: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 12)
  - Ohio: State of: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 13)
  - Ohio: State of: Subsidy: OSU's Portion: Memos, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 14)
  - Ohio Academy of Science: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Agricultural Research and Development Center: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Admissions Requirement Requests, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Budget Requests: Correspondence and Reports, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Capital Appropriations, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 19)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Capital Improvements: Correspondence and Reports, 1975-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 20)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Capital Plan for OSU: 1977-1983, 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 21)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Columbus Problem Solving Project, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 22)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Comprehensive Cancer Center and Capital Plan Requests, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 23)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1974 January-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 26)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1974 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 27)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 29)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0028, Folder 31)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1980 January-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 2)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Correspondence, 1980 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 3)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Developmental Education Activities of OSU, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 4)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Disciplinary Cases, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 5)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Energy Problems: Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 6)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: "Excellence Study", 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: "From the University to the Community", 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Graduate Program Review, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 9)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Lists of Special Grants received by OSU, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 10)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Losses in Federal Support, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 11)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Management Improvement Program: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 12)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Master Plan, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 13)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Master Plan: Comments from OSU Faculty, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 14)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 19)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 20)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 21)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 22)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Memorandums to Institutional Presidents, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 23)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Off-Campus Instructional Plan, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Ohio Instructional Grant Program Roles and Regulations, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: "Ohio Public Executives Program": Proposal, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 26)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Ohio State Capital Budget Requests, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 27)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: OSU Ten-Year Projection of Capital Needs (to 1990), 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Permission to Award the Associate of Arts Degree, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 29)